Novandra Zulfi Ramadhan



nodhzen@gmail.com



085292331838



linkedin.com/in/novandra-zulfi-ramadhan



http://inozura.github.io

Summary

I'm a software engineer who has 3 years of experience. I have several startup projects to help build systems on the frontend, backend, mobile and desktop application. Besides of that I also work as a freelancer on Upwork.

I have strong skills in Javascript/Typescript with several tools that I often use which is React, Next, React Native, Electron, Exspress, and Node. With these stacks I can create backend, frontend, mobile and desktop applications. some other stacks that I also master are Dart and Laravel using the Flutter and Laravel frameworks.

Experience



∧I Frontend Engineer

aiBase

Sep 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Developing frontend of machine learning self-service platform

Software Engineer (Freelance)

Upwork

Feb 2020 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Building Software app with JS/TS/Dart and PHP

🏀 Full Stack Engineer

Kleinanzeigen-Enhanced

Jun 2021 - Feb 2022 (9 months)

Building Ads management for eBay ecommerce with Microservice architecture

Wordpress Developer

PT.BimaSakti

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020 (1 year)

Education



Universitas Muria Kudus

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Technology 2019 - 2023

Licenses & Certifications



Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Excel - Dicoding Indonesia

Issued May 2020 - Expires May 2023

QLZ98ROG9X5D

9 Introduction to Programming Using Python - Dicoding Indonesia

Issued Apr 2020 - Expires Apr 2023 2VX3N6LM3XYQ

9 Machine Learning for Beginners - Dicoding Indonesia

Issued Oct 2020 - Expires Oct 2023 MRZMGK28KZYQ

9 Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Kognitif - Dicoding Indonesia

Issued Oct 2020 - Expires Oct 2023 QLZ9826WMX5D

Full-Stack JavaScript Developer - BuildWithAngga 2Vh4GfLTDR

Skills

Next.js • Redux.js • Express.js • Laravel • Node.js • Flutter • React Native • TypeScript • Dart • PHP